♪ 我的站到了 ♪
♪ This is my stop ♪
♪ 得下车了 ♪
♪ Got to get off ♪
♪ 还敢更挤嘛 ♪
♪ I might go pop ♪
借过
Excuse me
♪ 原谅我这么直 ♪
♪ I've got to be direct ♪
♪ 如冒犯请指教 ♪
♪ If I'm off, please correct ♪
♪ 你挡着我道了 ♪
♪ You're standing on my neck ♪
拽妹Daria
漫迪字幕组&@Daria拽妹黛薇儿
——·@严肃活泼小kk译制·——
瞧瞧这地方 这是哪?
Wow, look at this place. I wonder what it is
是图书馆吧 宝贝
I think it's the library, babe.
要是有钱
I could have sworn I had money
我就发誓先把预算留给屋顶翻修
budgeted for a new roof under capital improvements.
人人都会犯错
Oh, well. Everyone makes mistakes.
那是测谎仪吗?
Is that a polygraph machine?
是呀 抽奖赢回来的
Yes! Uh, I... won it in a raffle.
我不造到底上哪才能搞来维修费
I don't know where we'll get the money for repairs.
只能靠募捐啦
A fund-raiser, I guess.
来个70年代"我最摇摆"复古之夜么?
Boogie Bash '70s Revival Night?
行不通 迪斯科球被偷了
We can't. Someone stole the disco ball.
不行 我们得想点别的办法
No, we'll have to come up with something
能真正捕捉到朗岱尔高中生精彩生活的好办法
that truly captures the spirit of student life at Lawndale High.
现在 你们觉得为什么...
Now, why do you think it is
托尔斯泰认为自己把《战争与和平》写得如此...
that Tolstoy felt he had to make War and Peace so darned...
不讨人喜欢? Daria?
unpleasant? Daria?
这样一来就没人逼他写续集了么?
So no one would pester him to do a sequel?
早上好呀 祖国的花朵
Good morning, young people.
有一个坏消息要告诉大家
I have a very sad announcement.
图书馆要关闭一段时间
The library will be closed until further notice.
好极了 那是我唯一可以独处的好地方
Great. There goes the only place I can go to be alone.
艾玛你造那不是真的啦
Oh, you know that's not true.
为了筹集维修费 学校要搞一个中世纪展会
To raise money for repairs, the school will be presenting a medieval fair,
模拟中世纪的生活
simulating life in the middle ages.
好耶
Yeah!
急招志愿者
Volunteers are desperately needed.
拒绝做志愿者的人要自愿花10块钱买门票
Those who refuse to volunteer must voluntarily purchase a ticket for ten dollars
或自愿接受休学处分
or voluntarily face suspension.
祝大家有个愉快的一天
Have a nice day.
那大概是我听过最逗逼的事了
That may be the stupidest thing I've ever heard of.
没错 我们要参加
I know. We gotta go.
北鼻 这对人家来说很重要耶
Babe, this is very important to me.
《吉百利故事集》是经典佳作 我觉得我会演的很好
The Cadbury Tales are, like, classic, and I think I'd be great in the play.
就和我一起去试镜嘛
Just do the audition with me.
噢 宝贝...
Oh, babe...
没人能把情爱演得和你一样好了 Kevvy
Because nobody plays a love scene like you, Kevvy.
现在去练习吧
Now, go practice.
遵命 冲呀
Yes, ma'am. Break!
你的台词
Your lines!
他去哪?
Wow, where's he going?
我们要在展会上一起表演戏剧
We're going to be in a play together at the medieval fair.
挺好的
Oh. That's nice.
我们会是最受欢迎的一对
We'll be the most popular ones there.
那我就想嘛 反正我都要当志愿者啦
So I thought, if I have to volunteer anyway,
我应该也接受青少年该有的挑战
I might as well do something that challenges me as a teen
也许还能给其他不受欢迎的人的无聊生活增加点乐趣
and maybe bring some joy into the drab lives of others who are less popular.
所以 他们会搞一个晚宴剧场 放Ken Barry的戏剧
So, they'll have this dinner theater with a play by this guy, Ken Barry,
我要去给一个超萌的妹妹角色"艾米丽"试镜
and I'm going to audition for "Emily," the really cute sister.
"保佑我不受到报复吧..."
"Preserve me from the vengeance..."
很棒噢 宝贝
That's great, honey.
Daria 你在展会有什么工作?
Daria, what will you be doing at the fair?
负责待在房间里保持距离地观赏
Admiring it from the safe distance of my room.
Daria 这展会挺好的
Daria, this fair is for a very good cause.
每个人都应该去
Everyone should go.
你要去么?
Are you going?
老妈就不用去啦
That won't be necessary.
我是指所有学生
I meant every student.
那换梅姑来演咋样?
But what if Meryl Streep here gets the part?
梅丽尔·斯特里普: 1949年生 好莱坞女演员
没什么比你和爸在舞台脚灯那拼命喝彩更能表达支持了
Nothing says support like you and Dad leading a rousing cheer from the footlights.
再想想美味的晚宴
And just think of the delicious dinner.
我靠
Huh? Darn it!
要去试镜吗?
Should we try out for the play?
我们可能还会上海报呢
We might get on a poster.
我觉得时尚俱乐部不应该参加什么...
I don't think the Fashion Club should participate in activities
被迫交出衣柜自治权的活动
where you surrender wardrobe autonomy to someone else.
对 我们有更重要的事
Yeah. We have more important things to do.
没错
That's right.
我们去卡仕曼试试亮片礼服呗
Let's go to Cashman's and try on sequined gowns.
嗨 Sandi Tiffany 猜怎么着?
Hi, Sandi, Tiffany. Guess what?
你要转学?
You're transferring to a new school?
不是 我是要给《吉百利故事集》的艾米丽一角试镜
No. I'm trying out for the part of Emily in The Canterbury Tales.
真是奇了个怪啦 我也是
That is so weird. I am, too.
可是...
But...
是么? 我在报名表上没看到你的名字
Really? I didn't see your name on the sign-up sheet.
Quinn 你要是不想我去就直说
Quinn, if you don't want me to audition then just say so.
瞎说啥呀 Sandi
Stop that foolish talk, Sandi.
你去试镜我很开心
I'm happy you're auditioning.
你来演就等于我来演嘛 只不过实际上我没演罢了
If you get the part it'll be just like me getting it, only not.
亲们 说了你们也不信
Guys, you're not going to believe this.
Bret Strand刚约我出去了
Bret Strand just asked me out.
真哒? 你真的没意见么 Quinn?
Really? Is that okay with you, Quinn?
来看看这先锋派妇产科医生用废弃物创作的高价艺术品
Meet the avant-garde obstetrician who's turned his castoffs into big-ticket artwork.
接下来《呕心小世界: 脐带雕塑品 》
Umbilical cord sculpture, next on Sick, Sad World.
老爸?
Dad?
老爸
Dad!
能帮个忙么?
Could you help me with something?
说真的 Quinn 我没钱了
Honestly, Quinn, I'm just tapped out.
我也希望能帮上忙 可我身无分文
I wish I could, but I'm dead flat broke.
哪怕我有一快钱 你知道我肯定...
If I had a buck on me, you'd know I...
老爸 我需要有人帮忙排练台词
Da-ad! I need someone to help me rehearse my lines.
好吧 我上大学那会还演过吉尔登斯特恩
Oh, sure! You know, I played Guildenstern in college.
荒诞派代表作《罗森克兰茨和吉尔登斯特恩已死》中的角色
我还以为自己会紧张 可我镇定自若
I thought I'd be nervous, but I was cool as a cucumber.
那真有趣 因为我只有一点儿...
That's actually interesting because I'm just a little...
直到我走上舞台 发现自己站在众目睽睽之下
Until I walked on stage and found myself in front of the crowd standing room only.
我觉得太... 太暴露了
I felt so... naked.
爸 你这话一点用都没有
Dad, you're not helping me...
我僵住了 一句话都说不出
I froze. I couldn't say a word.
接着大家都在窃笑
Then it... started. The snickering.
他们的笑声把我轰走了 那些小婊砸
They laughed me off the stage, the jerks!
我去楼上练习
I'll go practice upstairs.
Quinn 亲爱的 其实那也没那么糟糕啦
Quinn, honey, it wasn't that bad really!
嘲笑几个月后就逐渐消停了 而且...
After a few months, the teasing tapered off and...
别说了
Stop!
也许我该去和她谈谈
Maybe I should go talk to her.
嘿 Ziggy
Hey! Ziggy!
英国摇滚音乐家David Bowie发行的专辑Ziggy Stardust
噢 帕拉蒙 深爱着我的人儿呀
Oh, Palamon, who has such love for me.
因此他就该... 屎
For which he is deserving of... death.
噢 帕拉蒙 深爱着我的人儿呀
Oh, Palamon, who has such love for me...
因此他就... 就该死 真酷
For which he's, like, deserving of death. Cool!
噢 帕罗曼 谁... 谁能记住这台词呀...
Oh, pal o'mine, who... who... who can remember all this?
可以开始了吗?
Uh, shall we begin?
行吧
Uh, I do, I guess.
现在我宣布你们结为夫妇
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
随着幸福的旋律奏起 帕拉蒙与艾米丽成婚
And thus with perfect bliss and melody, Palamon wedded Emily.
不要拒绝我嘛 小乖乖?
Hey! Why fight it, toots?
我们都是夫妻了
We're man and wife now.
做梦吧 Charles
Keep dreaming, Charles.
我愿意 Kevvy... 我是说 帕拉蒙
I do, Kevvy... I mean Palimony.
我也愿意
Yeah, me, too.
现在我宣布你们...
I now pronounce you...
好吧 伙计们
Okay, guys...
Brittany Brittany? Brittany
um, Brittany. Brittany? Brittany!
嗯?
Yes?
演得... 非常好
That was... very good.
不过现在该轮到别人试演了
But now it's time to give someone else a chance to audition.
好哒 走吧 Kevvy
Okay. Come on, Kevvy.
其实呢 我想让Kevin留在台上
Um, actually, I'd like Kevin to stay on stage.
Kevin 你演得确实不错
Kevin, you're really doing something special with Palamon.
可是... 我不就是帕拉蒙吗?
But... aren't I Palamon?
好的 下一个演艾米丽的是谁?
Now, who's next for Emily?
Quinn Quinn Morgendorffer
Ah, Quinn. Quinn Morgendorffer.
来了
Right here.
♪ 我会为自己编一个精致的花环 并放声歌唱 ♪
♪ I will make a dainty garland for my head and sing. ♪
哼着小调 哒啦哒啦
With a hey-nonny-nonny, tra-la, tra-la.
你能消停会不?
Would you give it a rest?
Daria 我要排练
Daria, I have to rehearse.
老妈让你来的 不赖我
It's not my fault Mom's making you come to this.
我才没有让你来呢
It's not like I want you there.
谢谢咯
Aw, thanks.
你俩别吵了
Stop it, you two.
Quinn Daria很开心能看你表演呢
Quinn, Daria's very happy to be seeing you in your play.
对吧 Daria?
Aren't you, Daria?
我会为自己编个精致的花环 并勒脖自尽
I will make a dainty garland for my neck and choke.
我希望其他女孩不会因为你得到这角色而失落
I hope the other girls weren't too disappointed that you got the part over them.
想想看 Sandi就没什么意见
Well, let's see. Sandi was really nice about it.
她说她老了
She said she's too mature
才不会嫉妒别人那无与伦比 难以置信又名不副实的运气
to get upset at somebody else's incredible, unbelievable, undeserved luck.
Brittany就嘟囔了几句
And Brittany just kind of made noises.
我猜她为你和Kevin一起表演这事
I guess she's speechless with joy that you and Kevin
开心到说不出话了
are going to be acting together.
奉告一句 Daria
For your information, Daria,
她自愿接送Kevin 好让他背下台词
she volunteered to drive him so he could work on his lines.
她有没有自愿给Kevin做个精巧的脑移植手术
Did she volunteer to get him a dainty transplant for his head
好让他背下台词?
so he could remember them?
熊孩子
Damn kids!
老不死
Crazy old jerk!
我希望那没让你分神
I hope that didn't disturb your concentration.
没有
Nah. I'm cool.
你懂的 我不想让任何事打扰你
'Cause, you know, I don't want anything to distract you from your performance.
我造 谢谢宝贝
I know, babe. Thanks.
宝贝... 那不是去学校的岔道么?
Uh, babe... isn't that the turnoff for school?
才不是呢
I don't think so.
不是吗? 哇 我真的很专心致志耶
Really? Wow. I am concentrating.
Daria? Quinn?
真奇怪 他们刚还在这
That's funny, they were here a minute ago.
嘿 亲 帽子上的尾巴不错嘛
Hey, my man! Cool threads.
你说我没用?
You calling me a wuss?
Linda Tom
Linda! Tom!
Helen Jake
Helen. Jake.
你们见过Sam和Chris了吗?
Have you met Sam and Chris?
孩子们 向Morgendorffer夫妇问好
Boys, say hello to Mr. and Mrs. Morgendorffer.
垃圾 废柴
You suck. You suck!
孩子们 快回来
Uh, kids, come back here.
恭喜Quinn能参演主角
Congratulations on Quinn getting the lead in the play.
谢谢 我听说竞争很激烈
Why, thank you. I heard the competition was pretty stiff.
可怜的Sandi演得不怎样
Well, poor Sandi's acting is a little subtle.
很明显 O'Neill老师要挑最优秀的人
Mr. O'Neill was obviously looking for someone over the top.
White同学 如果你能在这签名同意任何意外死亡...
Mr. White, if you'll just sign this waiver absolving Lawndale High
都与朗岱尔高中无关 我们就能开始啦
of any responsibility for your accidental death, we can start the fun!
比赛开始
Let the sport begin!
那个叫Jamie的
Well, if it isn't Jamie.
祝你挥杆挥得比翻书好
I hope you're better at wielding a lance than you are at opening a book.
你说对了我的名字 有人还叫过我...
You got my name right. Somebody actually...
下一位
Next!
谢谢你过来陪我
Thanks for meeting me here.
嘿 我本来就打算来的嘛
Hey, I wanted to come, remember?
再说我得离开家 Trent掌握了新的弦乐
Besides, I had to get out. Trent discovered a new chord.
哪位小可爱对牧歌有兴趣?
Would either of you lovelies be interested in a madrigal?
呸
No.
我是勇敢的Chuck大人 Chuck大人阳刚威猛 四肢发达...
I am the brave Sir Chuck, Sir Chuck, manly and strong and quick...
我要把你舌头割下来 舌头割下来 用棍子加以翻炒
I'm going to cut out your tongue, your tongue, and fry it up on a stick.
嘴贱死了 嘿 Andrea 你喜欢牧歌么?
Feisty. Hey! Andrea! You like madrigals?
五十年代经典儿童木偶剧《胡迪嘟迪秀》
别碰我 和胡迪都迪没两样的变态
Don't touch me, you Howdy-Doody-looking creep.
下午好 小伙子们
Good afternoon, young men.
你们将会通过"机会游戏"来掌握盈利原则
You're about to learn firsthand the profit-generating
principles by which games of chance...
好耶
Yes!
应该是"技能游戏"才对
Maybe I should say games of skill...
老天 Stacy 咋了? 你看起来很糟
God, Stacy, what's wrong? You look awful.
糟透了
Yeah. Really, really bad.
是Bret 第一次约会后他说他会打给我 可他一直没打
It's Bret. He said he'd call me after our first date but he never did,
我刚看到他了 我和他打招呼 可他装作没看到
and I just saw him and I said hi and he pretended like he didn't even see me.
真惨
Bummer.
嗯
Yeah.
穿着长裙好难走路
These long skirts are so hard to walk in.
对啊
I know.
Stacy 会好起来的
Stacy, it's gonna be all right.
他不值得 男人都这德性
He's not worth it. No guy is.
谢谢你们
Thanks, guys.
有闺蜜可以依靠真好
Oh, it's so great to know I can count on my true friends.
那他现在没有和别人约会?
So, then, he's not dating anyone now?
我不相信Quinn能超越你 拿到角色
I cannot believe Quinn got the part over you.
毫无真材实料
That's so wrong.
我相信她会演得很好
Oh, I'm sure she'll do a good job.
你觉得被万人迷吻了 你会从噩梦中醒来?
If Prince Charming kisses you, you think you'll wake up from this nightmare?
这有理有据 好么?
It's for a good cause, okay?
你一直这样给自己洗脑
You just keep telling yourself that.
或者让宫女来给你洗脑
Or have your ladies-in-waiting do it.
Mack王子在哪?
Where's Prince Mack?
是Barch老师的主意
It was Ms. Barch's idea.
你是班尼龙?
Are you Barney?
Barney是美国少儿节目 主角为紫色玩具小恐龙
杀了那龙 杀了那龙
Kill the dragon! Kill the dragon!
占卜未来 女生2刀 男生20刀
你会在青春期结婚
You will marry a man while still in your prime.
学生时代过后
Then, after putting him through school
花20年求他放弃该死的球员身份
and spending 20 long-suffering years begging him to turn off those damn Broncos
Broncos丹佛野马 职业美式足球球队
找点正经事干 结果他拍屁股走人
and get a real job, he'll walk out of your life,
原意: 在干净的地毯后边留下一串泥泞的脚印
留下一堆烂摊子
leaving a trail of muddy footprints behind on the freshly cleaned carpet.
可没有他你会过得更好 更加好
But you'll be better off without him. Much better off.
更加更加好
Much, much better off.
她就是个活生生的例子
And she's the living proof.
我们也去预测未来呗?
Should we get our fortunes read?
我不去 感知当下就已经够糟糕了
I'll pass. Knowing the present is bad enough.
那坐坐摩天轮?
Then how about a Ferris wheel ride?
我有没有很痛不欲生?
Do I look desperate to you?
罗马天主教势力与西欧封建主对穆斯林发动的侵略战争
十字军东征
Crusades! Crusades!
女士们... 听我唱一首《被误解的吟游诗人》
Ladies... wait till you hear the Ballad of the Misunderstood Minstrel.
这下我看起来痛不欲生了吧?
Do I look desperate to you now?
- 的确 - 走吧
- Yep. - Let's go.
你们太幸运了 还剩一个位置
You're in luck. One basket left.
嘿 快来听听我的歌
Hey, come on. Listen to my song.
是12行诗
It's only got 12 verses.
审判到了 审判到了
Inquisition! Inquisition!
拜托拜托 你让我上去嘛
Please, you gotta let me on.
不行 没位了
Can't. We're full up.
可我不想让别人看到我的眼睛
But I don't want anyone to see my eyes.
都红成这样了
They're this really weird shade of red.
对不起 出于安全考虑...
Sorry, safety regulations...
我付双倍的钱
I'll pay you double.
全员登陆
All aboard.
拜托 你不能这样安排
Excuse me. You can't do this.
我们是人类 妈蛋
We're human beings, damn it!
大家都以为我当时是剖腹产
And everyone thought I'd had a cesarean
因为Sandi的头型很圆润
because Sandi's head was so round and smooth
不像其他小孩那样扁平多棱角
and not flat and bumpy like the other babies.
我只用了两小时二十分钟就把Quinn生出来了
Well, my labor with Quinn was only two hours, 20 minutes,
所以她脑袋也很圆
so her head was quite round, too.
那就好 过35岁才生孩子的风险特高
That's great, especially since giving birth can be risky for women over 35.
现在我想让大家花一分钟设想一下观众的反应
Now, I want everyone to take a minute and visualize the audience.
当戏剧完美谢幕
As we finish our wonderful play,
他们品尝完美味的晚宴后起立鼓掌
they finish their delicious dinner and leap up as one in a standing ovation.
精妙绝伦 大家太棒啦
Brava! Brava! Everyone.
精妙绝伦 精妙绝伦
Brava, brava!
好的 低下头来缅怀可怜的詹姆斯·迪恩
Now, let's bow our heads for a moment and remember poor James Dean.
著名电影演员 美国十大文化偶像
噢 帕拉蒙 深爱着我的人儿呀
Oh, Palamon, who has such love for me;
我会为自己编一个精致的花环...
I will make a dainty garland...
Sandi? Tiffany? 你们来干嘛?
Sandi? Tiffany? What are you guys doing here?
我们来祝你好运
We came by to wish you luck.
不过你应该用不着
Not that you'll need it.
用不着
No way.
真哒?
You really think so?
你很有天赋 Quinn
You're really talented, Quinn.
我特别欣赏你独特的影响力
I especially like your unique inflections.
真的吗?
You do?
比如 给我们说句台词
Like, say a line for us.
好的
Well, okay:
"我会为自己编一个精致的花环 并放声歌唱"
"I will make a dainty garland for my head and sing."
懂我说的么?
See what I mean?
懂了
Oh, yeah.
懂什么 Sandi?
What do you mean, Sandi?
其他人会这么说
Well, anybody else would have said
"我会为自己编一个精致的花环"
"I will make a dainty garland for my head."
可你嘛 Quinn 凭你..精湛的演技 你是这么说的
But you, Quinn, with your... special talent, you said,
"我会为自己编一个精致的花环 并放声歌唱"
"I will make a dainty garland for my head."
我是说 你肯定很有天赋
I mean, it must be talent
因为你不会重读错单词嘛?
because you wouldn't emphasize the wrong words, would you?
肯定不会
No, of course not.
我不觉得咯
I didn't think so.
我真不敢相信她觉得自己能在选角上拼过你
I can't believe she thinks she should have gotten the part over you.
毫无真材实料
That's so wrong.
Quinn 看见Kevin了吗?
Quinn? Have you seen Kevin?
宝贝 我知道我们上学不用走高速
Now, I know we don't take a highway to school, babe.
你确定?
Are you sure?
不
Um... no.
人家甚至穿了破洞的天鹅绒背心 还是低胸的
I even wore my crushed velvet tank top, the one with the scoop neck,
可他还是没再约我出去
and he still didn't ask me out again.
要是你们人缘好就会明白的
If only you were popular enough to understand.
对 要是呗
Yes, if only.
这破摩天轮什么时候才能停?
When the hell is this ride going to be over?
这是什么?
What's this?
晚宴剧场 这是晚饭
Dinner theater; this is dinner.
没有餐具?
Don't we get utensils?
拜托 这是中世纪 老爷子
Hey, it's the middle ages, pops.
老爷子?
Pops?!
走啦 Jake
Come on, Jake.
你猜这火鸡剩下的部分去哪了?
What do you think happened to the rest of this turkey?
试着把这赖到"读写困难"头上
Try blaming this on dyslexia!
走吧 反正Quinn的戏剧马上就要开始了
Come on, Quinn's play's about to start, anyway.
下一位
Next!
可为毛? 是因为我说的话么?
But why? Is it something I said?
我的穿着么? 我还是死了罢
Something I wore? Oh, I wish I were dead.
听着 别因为些屌丝不再约你
Look, don't flush your entire world down the drain
就自甘堕落
just because some jerk didn't ask you out on a second date.
可能压根不是你的错
It probably had nothing to do with you anyway.
除非你真的做了蠢事
Unless you did something really stupid,
比如拿你的小问题和复杂的脑洞去烦他
like bore him with your petty problems and convoluted logic.
我怎么可能会那样做?
Why would I do that?
这真恶心 我快吐了
This is revolting. I think I'm going to be sick.
你还真的吃那玩意?
Hey, you going to eat that?
我会编一个精致的花环
I will make a dainty garland!
我会编一个精致的花环 我会编...
I will make a dainty garland. I will make...
嗨 Quinn 我就来给你打打气
Hi, Quinn. I just wanted to stop buy and wish you good luck.
我来给你鼓鼓劲
I want to wish you even better luck.
我来给你加加油
I want to wish you the best...
想帮忙的话就把Kevin找回来
Guys, if you want to help me, find Kevin.
他不在这 没人演帕拉蒙
He's not here and there's no one to play Palamon.
我来演帕拉蒙...
I'll play Palamon...
拜托
Come on, man...
不 我来演
No, me!
别再为人家撕逼了啦
Guys, don't fight over me.
非常时期需要非常手段
Desperate times call for desperate measures.
一种点人的童谣
点指兵兵 点到谁人做大兵
Eeny-meeny-miny-mo.
就你了 Jeffy 你只要念出帕拉蒙的台词就好
Now, Jeffy, all you have to do is read Palamon's lines
直到Kevin过来解释他为什么缺席
until Kevin gets here with his very good reason for sabotaging our play.
谢啦 Jeffy
Thanks, Jeffy.
我该演谁来着?
Who am I supposed to be again?
是一个叫P什么的?
It started with a "P"?
赎罪者
The Pardoner.
好的
Oh, yeah.
"我会为自己编一个精致的花环 并放声歌唱"
"I will make a dainty garland for my head and sing."
"欲望源自醉意"
"That lust proceeds from wine and drunkenness,
"考虑到酒后乱性有多反常..."
consider how drunken Lot pervertedly slept with..."
啊?
What?
"欲望源自醉意"
"That lust proceeds from..."
闭嘴
Stop!
都在窃笑 马勒戈壁
Snicker, snicker, snicker! Damn it!
谁在笑? 特么有那么好笑吗?
Who's laughing? What's so damn funny?
你这小...
Why you little...!
怎么回事?
What's going on?
那你觉得我该打给他吗?
Then, do you think I should call him?
没错 现在就打 好防止我去正当杀人
Yes, right now. Before I commit justifiable homicide.
绝逼热脸贴冷屁股
Must-stick-head-cold-water.
亲 能帮帮忙么?
Guys, can you help me out?
演练厅有点混乱
There's some kind of riot going on in the auditorium.
帮我看会咨询摊 我去找李校长
Just watch the information booth while I find Ms. Li.
糟了 我俩现在身负重任
Uh-oh, someone just put us in a position of responsibility.
今天突然变得邪恶起来啦
The day has suddenly turned sinister.
我只想让戏剧成功出演
I just wanted the play to go well.
当然啦
Of course you did.
瞧 在另一世 你是女人 这就是你为嘛这么多愁善感
See, in another life, you were a woman, which explains why you have feelings.
真的吗?
Really?
你抽的牌还说
Your cards also say that
你能和一个风韵犹存的同事共享天伦之乐
you and a still-attractive coworker have a chance for unparalleled bliss,
这能让你避免因性别相同而过穴居生活
provided you avoid the troglodytic behavior common to your sex.
真的? 何时?
Really? When?
很快
Very, very soon.
你们怎么不穿戏服?
Why aren't you wearing costumes?
我们穿了
We were,
不过把它们捐给中世纪美化暴力博物馆了
but we donated them to the Museum of Glorifying Violence In Medieval Times.
中世纪酷酷哒
The medieval times were cool.
空气更清新 也没那么拥挤
Yeah, the air was cleaner and there was less crowding
自从黑死病消灭了许多地方三分之一的人口
since the Black Death wiped out a third of the population in many places.
看到街上有牛车开过也是蛮酷
Must have been cool to see the ox carts rolling through the streets,
塞满了腐烂中的尸体
piled high with festering corpses.
罗宾汉其实活在14世纪
And the real Robin Hood actually lived in the 1300s.
国王爱德华二世搜捕了罗宾汉非法偷猎的鹿群
King Edward II busted Robin and his band of outlaws poaching deer.
不过 罗宾汉没有受到惩罚
But, rather than punish him,
爱德华赦免了罗宾汉 二人结为基友
he pardoned Robin and made him his special friend.
罗宾汉很感激 从那天开始他就坚持替国王洗澡澡
Robin was so grateful, from that day on he insisted on giving the king his bath.
英王亨利八世第二任妻子 伊丽莎白一世的生母
实际上 安娜·波莲也不漂亮
Actually, Anne Boleyn was no prize either.
她左手长了六根手指 脖子上还有大瘤子
She had six fingers on her left hand, a big mole on her neck,
千万别问我瘤子下边怎么了
and don't even ask me what was going on below that.
宝贝...
Um, babe...
现在我知道开去学校用不了这么长时间
now, I know it doesn't take this long to drive to school.
你确定?
Are you sure?
天啊
Oh, man!
欢迎微博关注
@漫迪字幕组